Shaul Leor-Lever

North / Tel Aviv +972-55-948-3039 in linkedin.com/in/saullever/ Saulus615@gmail.com

github.com/shaul615

Full Stack Web Developer, offering an outstanding ability to project manage, problem-solve and professionally train a diverse group. A mature and dynamic team member with 8+ years of valuable experience in global corporate work environments - specifically FMCG retail, manufacturing, marketing and sales. Project experience in full enterprise implementations of SAP to specific business system implementations.

Education

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT | 2019 - 2020 | DEVELOPERS.INSTITUTE | TEL-AVIV

Intensive Coding Bootcamp, focusing on Python and Backend Development. Hands-on full-stack coding with a working knowledge of HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Flask.

POSTGRADUATE DEGREE | 2003 - 2004 | UNIVERSITY OF THE WITWATERSRAND

Major: Business and Management, located in South Africa | Thesis topic: Bridging the digital divide

BACHELOR DEGREE | 2000 - 2003 | UNIVERSITY OF THE WITWATERSRAND

Majors: Information Systems and Economics, located in South Africa.

Hard skills

Project Management | Big Data analysis | Google API | AWS | SAP | Python | KRONOS | OOP | GitHub | MS Office | IOS 9 | Linux | Social Media | SEO | Internal Communications | Animations | Multimedia presentations | Employee training | Advanced driving | Teleprompter | Pycharm IDE | Visual Studio Code IDE | 3D printing | UX/UI

Experience

PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT ASSISTANT | DRAGONWELL MEDIA | SACRAMENTO, CALIFORNIA | 2018 - 2020

- Designed scalable product marketing and sales material. Managed social media accounts for multiple clients, generating interest for existing and upcoming product and service releases.
- Analysed key aspects of the business to evaluate factors driving results and summarised into presentations
- Integrated and quality tested new gps reference features into existing mobile apps
- Assistant to Chief Product Architect for daily project office functions and administrative duties

BUSINESS ANALYST | ECOMMUNICATE | SOUTH AFRICA | 2016-2018

- Project management and Front-End development for an online responsive platform for 800+ managers to recognise 14 000+ non-PC based employees and allow them to redeem rewards through their mobile app.
- Automated and encrypted a PDF employee contract process from design conceptualization to client delivery
- Designed and implemented a CRM system utilized by over 18 000 decentralised users
- Analyzed company training methods and made adjustments to rectify issues, increase efficiency and exceed training goals, resulting in 80% increase in product usage.

SYSTEMS MANAGER | DIS-CHEM | SOUTH AFRICA | 2008-2016

- Responsible for more than 4 projects per year from initial research and conceptual design through testing and implementation phases. Responsible for systems supporting, employee life cycle
- Migrated legacy HRIS payroll system to SAP platform in 4 months, minimized business impacts
- Implemented a recruitment process reducing the average time to hire from 2 months to 14 days.
- Updated quality control standards, methods and procedures to improve audit compliance and visibility.

HUMAN RESOURCES OFFICER | UNILEVER SOUTH AFRICA | 2004-2008

- Administered SAP master data and inducted manufacturing and engineering employees
- Negotiated agreements between employees to clarify misunderstood directions and resolve conflicts affecting performance. Graduate recruitment and mentoring
- Compiled and published internal workplace communications in 12 different languages.

Languages

English: Mother Tongue Hebrew: Conversational Dutch: Conversational